mbarendezvous.com 2018-02-22

# MBA Rendezvous - Privacy Policy

April 19, 2017 @ 11:20 AM 

April 19, 2017 @ 11:20 AM

## **Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**

MBARendezvous.com is an internet service that allows users to create personal web profiles and communicate and share content with friends and other users. To help our members identify and interact with each other, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors. MBARendezvous.com members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

MBARendezvous.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@mbarendezvous.com](mailto:privacy@mbarendezvous.com).

**Process of Information Collection and Use by MBARendezvous.com**

MBARendezvous.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the MBARendezvous.com service. MBARendezvous.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in connecting with each other. Further, in order to facilitate commerce, we collect credit card information, member's address, or bank information only from those who choose to join MBARendezvous.com.

MBARendezvous.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

User Profile information including members' pictures and user names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the MBARendezvous.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join MBARendezvous.com, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on MBARendezvous.com with each other through the MBARendezvous.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, MBARendezvous.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, interests and schools where users may have attended.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings".

From time to time, MBARendezvous.com or a partner may advertise on MBARendezvous.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address in order to participate or receive a response from MBARendezvous.com or one of its partners. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from or expressed an interest in.

**Use of Cookies**

MBARendezvous.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from MBARendezvous.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that MBARendezvous.com allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertiser's use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the MBARendezvous.com Privacy Policy.

**Links**

MBARendezvous.com contains links to sites. MBARendezvous.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on MBARendezvous.com.

**Security**

MBARendezvous.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords MBARendezvous.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on MBARendezvous.com, please email us at [info@mbarendezvous.com](mailto:info@mbarendezvous.com)

****Sharing and Disclosure of Information MBARendezvous.com Collects****

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, MBARendezvous.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by MBARendezvous.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the MBARendezvous.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. MBARendezvous.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of MBARendezvous.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

****Changes in Privacy Policy****

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [info@mbarendezvous.com](mailto:info@mbarendezvous.com)

Crucial Dates, You Should not Miss

[**Manav Rachna International Institute  
of Research**](http://www.mbarendezvous.com/mba-institute/manav-rachna-international-institute-of-research-and-studies/)   
Admissions Open for all MBA programme at Manav Rachna International Institute of  
Research and Studies.  |  [**CII School of Logistics Amity University, Delhi and Mumbai**](http://www.mbarendezvous.com/mba-institute/CII/)   
Admissions Open at CII School of Logistics Delhi and Mumbai campus, Apply Now!  
---|---  
Admissions open for MBA programmes at GITAM. Application Deadline is February 20, 2018  |  [**XIME**](https://admission.nopaperforms.com/xavier-institute-of-management-entrepreneurship?utm_source=MBARendezvous&utm_medium=Banner&utm_campaign=Admissions_2018)   
Application Last Date for Online Submission - February 25, 2018  
Apply for PGDM & PGDM-IB Programmes. Admissions Open for 2018 Apply Now! |  [**MDI Murshidabad**](http://www.mdim.ac.in/ApplyOnline.htm?utm_source=mbarendezvous&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=admissions_MDI%20Murshidabad_2018)   
Applications for PGPM 2018-20 at MDI Murshidabad are open   
Last Date to Apply for IPE, Hyderabad is 17 February, 2018  |  [**IMI New Delhi**](https://www.imi.edu/delhi/?utm_source=mbarendezvous&utm_medium=banner)   
Admissions Open for Executive PGDM at IMI, New Delhi. Application closes on March 1, 2018.  
Last date extended to 11 February, 2018. Apply Now.  |  [**SDMIMD**   **Mysore**](http://sdmimd.ac.in/)   
Application for PGDM 2018-20 at SDMIMD is open till February 28, 2018   
Admission 2018 Open for MBA at Birla Global University  |  [**KIIT School of Management**](http://bit.ly/2nwIEg3)   
Admissions Open for MBA at KIIT School of Management through CAT/ MAT/ GMAT/ ATMA/ CMAT/ XAT
